

## Pawel Wozniak

# MASTER OF SCIENCE IN AUTOMATICS AND ROBOTICS

#### **DETAILS**

0

Sloneczna 1, 64-800 Chodziez



+48 732 012 986



pawel.wozniak.wp@gmail.com



https://github.com/Pablo-Saxoo

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- JavaScript/JQuery
- React
- Python language: pandas, librosa, numpy, sqlite3
- Knowledge of ML/AI: Tensorflow-Keras/Pytorch/Scikit-learn
- SQL/Git/Github/Latex/Microsoft
- Availability and commitment

#### FOREIGN LANGUAGES

Polish: Native

English:

B2

Upper Intermediate

#### **HOBBIES**

Jazz music enthusiast. I started my musical adventure at the age of 7 with the piano. I played the clarinet, trumpet and percussion but the saxophone became the chosen one. In my free time, I learn new improvisations, read and go to the gym.

A passionate saxophonist, an engineer by profession. Perfectionist. Experience as frontend developer and python programmer. Interested in the field of WEB 3.0, blockchain, artificial intelligence and machine learning. Passionate about modeling and 3D printing. Always thirsty for new knowledge.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

June 2019 - November 2020

### Constructor Engineer - Podanfol, Podanin

- Creating 2D and 3D technical documentation of machine parts in Inventor and Autocad.
- Automation and optimization of production processes.
- Prototyping and operation of a 3D printer.
- Planning and implementation of the reconstruction project of one of the factory premises using a laser scanner. The aim of the project was to create a 3D model of the room using BIM technology. A Faro scanner and the Revit program were used to recreate the room.

January 2023 - June 2023

## Constructor Engineer – Poly-clip system, Hattersheim

- Constructing 3D technical documentation of machine parts in SolidWorks
- Measurement and analysis of machine vibrations
- 3D printer renovation

#### **EDUCATION**

October 2017 - June 2022

## Master Engineer Automation and Robotics Poznan University of technology

- Bachelor's thesis: Robot arm control algorithm with collision avoidance
- Master's thesis: Relationship between selected physical quantities operating in a saxophone mouthpiece and the quality of the sound produced
- Master's degree specialization: Robots and Autonomous Systems

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy.